# Tejesh Reddy

Tempe, Arizona, United States



tejeshreddy111@gmail.com



+16028152070



linkedin.com/in/tejeshreddy1

## **Summary**

I am a first-year student currently pursuing masters in computer science at Arizona State University. As a graduate services assistant at ASU, I work on open-source tools/frameworks related to web crawlers and containerization solutions. I am a passionate problem solver with over 2+ years of professional software development experience in the areas of software engineering, backend, and infrastructure engineering.

Check my portfolio at: https://tejeshreddy.github.io/

#### **Experience**

### \*cvs Software Engineer

**CVS Health** 

Feb 2023 - Present (6 months)

- Software Engineer contributing to the Pharmacy Benefits Management (PBM) team at CVS.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop an UiPath framework that automatically processes patient claims using business pipeline, resulting in a 30% reduction in processing time and a decrease in error rates.
- Implemented a robust RESTful service architecture to manage, deploy, and trigger over multiple RPA robots, ensuring seamless integration with existing systems and enhancing process automation efficiency.

#### Is A Pulson Schools of Engineering Arizona Statio

#### **Teaching Assistant**

Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering at Arizona State University

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022 (5 months)

**Teaching Assitant for Courses:** 

CSE 259: Logic in Computer Science (Prof. Steven Osburn)

CSE 355: Introduction to Theoretical Computer Science (Prof. Gennaro De Luca)



#### **Graduate Research Assistant**

Ira A. Fulton Schools of Engineering at Arizona State University

Nov 2021 - Aug 2022 (10 months)

Department: SEFCOM

- Assisting in a research project that aims to perform security analysis of large-scale firmware images and embedded systems when rehosted on a Linux-based virtual machine.
- Developed and deployed over 50 data pipelines on Kubernetes that aims on downloading over 80k firmware images from supported 100+ hardware vendors.
- Integrating several binary analysis workflows to help reverse engineer and analyze a targeted threat on firmware images.



#### Arizona State University

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

Department: UASP

• Tutoring undergraduate/graduate students in areas of computer science, programming, math, statistics, and SQL.



#### Software Engineer

Unbxd Inc., A Netcore Company

Jul 2019 - Aug 2021 (2 years 2 months)

Unbxd is an AI powered commerce search which creates a relevant and personalized user shopping experience

- Building data pipelines using PySpark and Hadoop on AWS EMR to facilitate data ingestion to power search
- Integration of Unbxd search, autosuggest and recommendation libraries to customer e-commerce sites
- Contributing to the design and development of Unbxd Search/Autosuggest and Recommendation Libraries
- Developing intelligent product recommender systems to rank products based on NLP and statistical approaches
- Collaborating with the internal teams for developing uptime and scheduler monitoring dashboard and visualization tools

#### Java Software Engineer

Hindustan Aeronautics Limited

Jan 2019 - Feb 2019 (2 months)

- Assisted the engineering department to develop a technical snag(mechanical error) consolidation software to avoid manual error while collecting mission-critical information
- Designed and developed webpages for workflow management with an aim to achieve a faster and hassle-free allocation of task

#### sol Globe Web Developer

SdlGlobe Technologies Pvt Ltd (Formerly SmartDrive Labs Technologies India Pvt Ltd)

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018 (2 months)

#### Education

# Arizona State University

Masters of Science - MS, Computer Science

Aug 2021 - Present

# PES University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Science and Engineering Aug 2015 - May 2019

# 🛞 Ryan International School, Noida

2003 - 2015

# **Licenses & Certifications**

RCR - Engineers Responsible Conduct of Research - CITI Program 52368019

### **Skills**

Data Structures • MySQL • Python (Programming Language) • Java • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Data Engineering • Docker Products • Kubernetes • REST APIs • Distributed Databases